# RUSTAM ZIYADOV

# **FULL-STACK SOFTWARE DEVELOPER**

rystam.com ◆ github.com/zyderus ◆ zyderus@gmail.com ◆ +7 925 849 2225

# **SKILLS**

## **Programming Languages**

JavaScript, TypeScript, React, Node, Express, SQL, MongoDB, GraphQL, HTML, CSS/SCSS, Dart

#### Frameworks & Libraries

Express, React, Next, Node, Flutter

## **Tools**

Git, Figma, Webpack, Gulp, Redux, Jest, Testing Library, Prisma, typeORM, Firebase, Heroku, Netlify, Vercel

#### Languages

Russian, English

#### Frameworks & Libraries

Express, React, Next, Node, Flutter

# **PROFILE**

Recruitment Agency specializing in construction and security sectors. Searching for clients, leads management, service promotion, presentations, financial analysis and accounting. As well, as developed and maintained web technology to automate recruitment processes. Implemented and monitored security and fraud prevention systems for online transactions to decrease fraudulent activity on e-commerce servers of company

## RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

**Developer @ Tron Movies project**June 2021 – Present

- Develop front-end and design
- Develop back-end and microservices
- Setup database to query and manipulate data

Developer @ Tron Movies project

June 2021 – Present

- Develop front-end and design
- Develop back-end and microservices
- Setup database to guery and manipulate data

Developer @ Tron Movies project

June 2021 – Present

- Develop front-end and design
- Develop back-end and microservices
- Setup database to query and manipulate data

Developer @ Tron Movies project

June 2021 – Present

- Develop front-end and design
- Develop back-end and microservices
- Setup database to guery and manipulate data

# **EDUCATION**

## University of Colorado

1997 – 2000 Boulder, CO, USA

- Develop front-end and design
- Develop back-end and microservices
- Setup database to guery and manipulate data

Developer @ Tron Movies project

June 2021 - Present